snappa.io 2019-12-12

# Privacy Policy - Snappa

Nosco Media Inc. (hereinafter referred to as “Snappa”) has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to helping our users better understand what information we collect about them and what may happen to that information. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

By accepting this Privacy Policy you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of Snappa’s [Terms and Conditions](https://snappa.com/terms). 

Subject to the requirements of applicable law, we strive to provide a consistent set of privacy practices. 

####  Information We Collect 

#####  Non-Personally Identifiable Information 

We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on our website using cookies and other devices. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. This information may include (but is not limited to) the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, and your IP address. Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. 

#####  Personally Identifiable Information 

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs. 

Snappa only collects such personal information that is necessary for you to use our services. This personal information includes, but is not limited to, first and last name, mailing address, zip/postal code, email address, financial information, and other personal information necessary to satisfy legal requirements. 

As a matter of policy, we will never sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. 

We have an international presence, and you agree that to facilitate the use of our services, your personal information may be stored and processed on our computers in the United States of America & Canada. The laws on holding personal data in the United States may differ from Canadian law but as we explain below, we will hold and transmit your information in a safe, confidential and secure environment. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area or a country which restricts data transfers outside of that jurisdiction or region without your consent, you consent to your personal information being transferred outside of the European Economic Area or your country for processing or storage by or on behalf of us. 

####  Our Use of Your Information 

Any of the personal information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To process transactions – (your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the services requested)
  * To improve our website - (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service - (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To send periodic newsletters or other promotional emails may be sent to you from us. Users have the option to unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time and at their sole discretion.

Your personal information will not be used for any other purpose without your consent.

####  Our Disclosure of Your Information 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. 

We may also release your personal information when we believe the release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information or information that has been rendered anonymous may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

####  Security 

Snappa treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by members inside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the internet. 

####  Accuracy 

We will try to ensure that information about you is accurate, complete and up-to-date. However, please inform us of any change of name, address or other information. In the event you have questions about the accuracy of factual information we have collected about you, you will have access to that information in order to verify and update it. 

####  Access 

If you have any questions about the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information or if you simply want to know whether we have any of your personal information on file, you may contact Snappa support at contact@snappa.com. Except in limited circumstances, as specifically provided by applicable privacy legislation, we can tell you whether we hold personal information about you. If we do hold personal information about you, you may request that this information be erased. 

####  Notice 

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments and our need to accurately reflect our data collection and disclosure practices. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on February 15, 2017.
